zktskhan: hello
Keyeh: good evening dude whats up
andrewfashion: mr hotz, i can make you IG famous
dorkmo: thumbs up lets do this
sl4ckerman: second stream of the day? nice
goofe7: #1
480i: Stream is smooth now
Aocuser: seeing you
Keyeh: webcam freezes sometimes but I see you
eugenedream: sup
480i: Spoke too soon. Oops.
eugenedream: I watched your simulation talk at sxsw and it has me rattled
AideTechBot: do you hire interns
480i: Yeah the talk was good
AideTechBot: ;)
NclxGaming: Are you having fun programming inside the simulation?
480i: I think I would have to pay to bring geohots pure leaf tea. Does that make me a geohot shill idk
rr00mm11: Any reason you're not using a tool like modernizer for that?
acheesedanish00: 2 streams in one day?
acheesedanish00: fuck yeah
chase_higgins: Hey George what are you porting?
Keyeh: qira, a debugger he wrote
chase_higgins: Sick
Keyeh: not frozen
ScrubLifeChoseMe: welcome back
lazystring: hey
mattikaldi: fresh cut?
anatoly1974: did u find God Yet George ??
davidsit_site: well thanks for thinking of us and dropping online for a short bit. hope you have a good night
anatoly1974: how is this basic when is it is machine code ??? @georgehotz
NclxGaming: What's your #1 programmer in the world (or people that inspire you - if any - because of their skills)? yourself? :P
Keyeh: its BASIC dude
davidsit_site: basic machine code.
davidsit_site: basically machine code
davidsit_site: lol
NonTrivial778: GeoHot what do you think about password managers ?
zacoaa: Do you like java?
davidsit_site: no java
cIvIcbooks: kernalshark has a interesting trace reader
ViktorTV: do not shit talk java
ViktorTV: java is great if uour goal is to have a stable job
ViktorTV: 100k a year easy life if you know java well
BradyLange: Java is good stuff
ViktorTV: however if you desire anything more then java is shit
davidsit_site: java was my 3rd language
lazystring: CHAT IS DEAD
th3_maj0r: 2 stream in a day wow
Keyeh: LMAO
Masboy_: !uptime
glitchedoutt: Prolog was invented for perpetual employment of monks
NclxGaming: What was the word he said? lol
davidsit_site: hotz is going to automate all jobs and make a religion? I thought that was a joke....
zacoaa: Im tryna figure it out
davidsit_site: I mean. I'm down to help automate everything. I'll not help past that
th3_maj0r: Metroment
glitchedoutt: This stream is brought you by capitalism
Keyeh: so its basically water
th3_maj0r: metroment has 0kcal
magician2378: this stream is brought to you by the simulation
TheFrozenTruth: @georgehotz what chair do you use?
z0di4ckx: hey
NclxGaming: I don't think why someone would want to learn programming to find a job
Rydberggg: what can you play on piano ?
480i: Y u no aeron
glitchedoutt: Herman Miller Aeron
davidsit_site: @nclxgaming. elaborate please?
th3_maj0r: why stream drops so many frames
karelomab: Brought to you by Ice Tea
anatoly1974: what is your speciality in the realm of coding ??
nightknight0000: close laptop lid, will fix all your lag issues
xcodevn: turn off preview help a bit
NclxGaming: Brother if you need money why would you spend so much effort just to get a job? You learn programming to CREATE and to do stuff that are actually worth it not to get a stable job.
th3_maj0r: u need to restrat i think. next time we will see
480i: @nclxgaming Don’t you need both
glitchedoutt: Material Design
Knarez: needs pretty colors Kappa
ABuffSeagull: if you're gonna use React, use React Hooks, it's quite a bit better
davidsit_site: @nclxgaming agreed
ABuffSeagull: although I still love Vue
favvs13: @georgehotz TriHard 7
BradyLange: ScaredyCat
acheesedanish00: I'll sponsor you geo
lbucci3: start drinking Bang! a bunch of girls on IG get sponsored .. :p
ABuffSeagull: React Hooks is a more functional structure, instead of OOP with components. Which is nice, since React really pushes for functional patterns
kakurai: hey @georgehotz , I'm a huge fan of yours. Greetings from Brazil.
anatoly1974: All I want to know is what the hell is that machine code doing there ??
lbucci3: another Brazilian
FugaxOfficial: hello
Knarez: when was the last time you used xmonad
ffthgezgxjkndd: !uptime
ffthgezgxjkndd: danke
Keyeh: python implements integer by default?
Keyeh: bigInt*
anatoly1974: some 30 minutes in @ffthgezgxjkndd
Keyeh: never actually look into it
NclxGaming: For how long did you work at Facebook? Thanks for quitting btw
NclxGaming: Could you imagine this guy working @facebook? NotLikeThis
Keyeh: dangerous energy to drink OMEGALUL
acheesedanish00: not bad actually geo
luhartt: bang gets u wired
lbucci3: Bang - all IG babes drink it
davidsit_site: yeah. @nclxgaming. boredom increasing the time spent on Facebook hours graph.
anatoly1974: FIRQ,IRQ
thylacinev: do you code during most of your free time?
OArtero: @georgehotz do you use cherry Blue keys in your kb ?
Enm1ty: no way those are blues
Enm1ty: sound like buckling spring
Enm1ty: topre?
somewhere_rains: !uptime
Keyeh: inb4 its not even mechanical
NclxGaming: Lol. @davidsit_site Nice formula (assuming you meant georgehotz's boredoom time)
Enm1ty: monkaS
AugTV: What are u currently working on?
jay_al97: hey you're back?
jay_al97: this is the second stream today?
Dsplits: messy code
acheesedanish00: qira port to python 3
jonahglover: jonahglover subscribed at Tier 1.
NclxGaming: I know who Siraj will call when he needs some coding help
chase_higgins: Do you do all your programming from the command line?
davidsit_site: ....kmsl @nclxgaming
jonahglover: @georgehotz were you listening to sunny day real estate during your SLAM stream? One of the songs sounded like "Circles". Related: am I as good as George Hotz if I listen to early 2000s emo when I am programming?
Hamled2: Do you have any test coverage configured for qira?
Hamled2: it says passing on my computer
Hamled2: browser cache
ferrari_pizza: hi geohot hi all
anatoly1974: can u tell us what project r u working on at least we are confused !
nmuntz_: @georgehotz I noticed that qemu 2.5.1 is not compatible with python3 so to build it it requires python2 installed. how hard would it be to port your patches to the latest qemu version?
erichtp: Are we at a million on instagram yet
nomadicpatch: !uptime
Bloumbs: Bloumbs subscribed at Tier 1.
chase_higgins: Nope not a million yet lol
erichtp: At least he fixed the frames dropping
Gtxgaming23: i hate python....
davidsit_site: as it drops
erichtp: Two streams one day PogChamp
Bloumbs: @georgehotz what was it you were doing with the tesla comp you posted on your instagram George?
davidsit_site: didn't Tesla just give away a car to someone who hacked it
erichtp: @davidsit_site idk if it was Tesla themselves but someone won it in Pwn2Own
ferrari_pizza: I did not fall in love with python either
erichtp: I like Python it’s like c++ without the curly brackets and shit just works lol
davidsit_site: what languages beat python?
ferrari_pizza: ruby
ferrari_pizza: but it's smaller
ferrari_pizza: libs
davidsit_site: but better is subjective
geobitz: jailbreak the tesla the people deserve it
geobitz: plus a big shots fired toward elon
Hamled2: I've taken a liking to ruby as well, especially I think it works better as an "upgraded shell scripting" language over python
erichtp: Tesla has the holiday dances you can make yours fortnite emote LUL
davidsit_site: like if I said Ida is better ( because I have no experience with q), it's subjective....sell the tesla to fund my projects after unrooting it
ferrari_pizza: of course it's just a personal choice,
NclxGaming: People talking shit about college yet the best programmers I know went all to college O_o
NclxGaming: What do you guys think about GoLang?
ferrari_pizza: whattsapp runs erlang
Irkanu: heyo, just got in. did you finish the font config cache exploit?
ferrari_pizza: old but great
Hamled2: I've been looking at building binary analysis tools (working with a new book from No Starch about it). What are the biggest challenges you've had trying to make an IDA competitor?
tribegvng: g man
davidsit_site: thank you for explaining. I misunderstood its use case.
ferrari_pizza: in too stupid for reversing in 2019
tribegvng: do you like ghidra?
atomfighter10101: Hi @georgehotz
davidsit_site: didn't touch it. did you?
Hamled2: it just takes time ferrari_pizza. My best advice for getting better at reversing is to learn programming -- a lot of reversing something "easily" is knowing what the developer originally was trying to do
DrewHintz: @Hamled2 take a look at Ghidra, it's great. No debugger yet though.
atomfighter10101: @georgehotz what is that awesome debugger?
bcrscahh198987: wow assembly
mikey9988: Assembly monkaS
ferrari_pizza: I'm coding in java
bcrscahh198987: what kind of assembly? x86?
tribegvng: @DrewHintz yeah everyone is loving it
Hamled2: Yeah I saw MalwareTech working with it, haven't used it myself yet
bcrscahh198987: which ISA?
atomfighter10101: Is this web assembly
Hamled2: ferrari_pizza have you tried reversing any java code
ferrari_pizza: sometimes in c for esp8266
bcrscahh198987: web assembly rofl
bcrscahh198987: web assembly is a joke, I'm sure of it
r1c1c: hi youtube
tribegvng: unless it has a secret backdoor
tribegvng: lmao
bcrscahh198987: why would people reinvent assembly in javascript
rage_au: what is he doing
ferrari_pizza: @hamled2 no, did not
Hamled2: ferrari_pizza one way to do "reversinG" in an easier fashion than straight-on assembly (x86 or JVM bytecode) would be to take a chunk of Java code, and remove all the variable names (replace them with random stuff) and try to work out what the code does
brevan04: Same bat time same bat channel
Hamled2: it's practicing a lot of the same skills I think
prakyath_kantharaju: prakyath_kantharaju subscribed with Twitch Prime.
ferrari_pizza: I've got 2 projects for android I'm working on, so maybe later
atomfighter10101: Oh its your own debugger looks great man
bcrscahh198987: does hotz stream games
bcrscahh198987: or only programming
Hamled2: keep working on those, that's also great practice :)
r1c1c: @bcrscahh198987 yes he does sometimes
davidsit_site: only fortnight
tribegvng: whats the diff between Ghidra and Qira?
NclxGaming: Which language did they use to program the simulation?
davidsit_site: (kidding) @bcrscahh198987
bcrscahh198987: lol
ferrari_pizza: @hamled2 I would also like to make my sony vcr read my android filesystem
bcrscahh198987: What' sthat web ap?
ferrari_pizza: :)
davidsit_site: we don't use Sony products in this household
atomfighter10101: @georgehotz Can qira run on windows10
Hamled2: that would be interesting, might be possible!
bcrscahh198987: nvm, it's qira
tribegvng: Runs it any browser
tribegvng: in*
Hamled2: tribegvng, Ghidra focuses on static analysis tools for reversing, where as Qira is a dynamic analysis tool primarily, or that's certainly where it stands out
ferrari_pizza: @i don't actually know who Filesystem is my SD card...
bcrscahh198987: qira is for application audit?
ferrari_pizza: those Linux ones...
tribegvng: I think i need to understand programming fully before i reverse shit right?
Hamled2: ferrari_pizza ext4 maybe?
ferrari_pizza: yes..
tribegvng: at like an expert level
ferrari_pizza: ntfs also possible...
Hamled2: tribegvng I think it helps a lot. They're very related skills so it'd be hard to be an expert at one without having decent skills at the other (maybe not specifics like assembly reversing, if you've never programming assembly, but in general)
tribegvng: i'm shit at programming though so its probably not gonna happen
erichtp: @tribegvng how would you know how to go backwards without going forwards first?
Hamled2: just keep working on it tribegvng
ferrari_pizza: Linux kernel is flexible in reading FS
tribegvng: understandable @Hamled2
Gtxgaming23: what is he programming
Hamled2: ferrari_pizza usually NTFS on linux is done through FUSE so not actually in the kernel
karelomab: FAT32 ftw
ferrari_pizza: year, vcr reads fat32
Hamled2: for flash drives?
ferrari_pizza: yes
karelomab: he said he has a SD card
karelomab: its 99% fat32 :/
Hamled2: ah
Significantbits: What vim colorscheme is this?
tribegvng: Just got a new M.2 drive damn they are fast
tribegvng: also risking it with no backup drive
karelomab: i mean
karelomab: you would use m2 for OS
atomfighter10101: So qira preforms a dynamic analysis on a running program in linux
karelomab: you put your data on a regular 3.5"
tribegvng: yeah i'm using it for OS but my company bought it so i just got a 1TB drive
tribegvng: have a 6tb backup
Hamled2: I think it runs it with qemu atomfighter10101, not sure if that means it allows for other guests than just linux
Gtxgaming23: isnt strace better than this qira>
Hamled2: Gtxgaming23 I think qira has an strace output window within it...
Gtxgaming23: ok
atomfighter10101: Thanks @Hamled2 .
tribegvng: It's strange though it disables some of the sata ports
tribegvng: wonder if thats related to the board
ferrari_pizza: just use cemu for super mario cart
karelomab: really? i have m2 and my sata ports are fine
Hamled2: the motherboard only has so many SATA channels, so it's redirecting one of them
tribegvng: i'm running am4
karelomab: hmm
Hamled2: unless it's using the pci-e bus
Hamled2: depends on the m.2 implementation i think?
Hamled2: was it b-key or m-key
tribegvng: i'm not sure
vtcN_: m2. us a form factor
vtcN_: *is
Hamled2: yeah but multiple m.2 options support variously SATA-based drives and NVMe PCI-E based drives
tribegvng: I think its on this specific msi board
Bloumbs: I feel like this stream is George inside a glass room, and were all on the outside chatting and watching him code lol
Bloumbs: not in like a bad way
Bloumbs: love it lol
karelomab: glass room?
karelomab: LOL
Hamled2: which I think would determine if a SATA port needed to be disabled to use the M.2 slot or not, but I haven't run into this scenario before idk
davidsit_site: back to your Black Mirror episode
ferrari_pizza: glass is broken.. 😂
Bloumbs: room. box. whatever
davidsit_site: EleGiggle
brevan04: He low key is going to get the weed
karelomab: you mean Class room
tribegvng: getting the vvyanse pill
tribegvng: :d
ables91: not again
karelomab: looks like george is going backwards
karelomab: first there was qira
karelomab: now there is half of it xD
Hamled2: nice TODO message
karelomab: good old hardcoded magic numbers
chase_higgins: George check slack lmao
davidsit_site: in py3
ables91: sickkkkkkkk
chase_higgins: Er discord
andrewfashion: what in gods name is he building lol
andrewfashion: what is QIRA?
vtcN_: how many magic numbers are there now? a million?
mikey9988: every number is a magic number besides 0 and 1 monkaS
karelomab: that's future george problem
ferrari_pizza: I like how George is on his trail to really get an epic coder
mikey9988: what exactly is he working on @ferrari_pizza
ferrari_pizza: ollidebug and Ida are epic in a way
tribegvng: i like how people on the commai yt chan are like what keyboard do you use
tribegvng: like it makes you a good programmer
jgab19: !uptime
ferrari_pizza: his timeless debugger python3
ferrari_pizza: compatible
RockyJ0: Hey!
tomayyo: !uptime
tribegvng: is this anything similar to how groups crack the netflix encyption? or is that entirely web based?
tribegvng: they dont have any specific file to crack
Hamled2: well the content is delivered encrypted to the browser and decrypted by some native code module, I think
jagger_rsw: so after ai, cars, instagram George is back working on security?
Hamled2: so they would be reverseing and "cracking" that module
ferrari_pizza: what kinda crypto in Netflix?
tribegvng: its thier own format
Hamled2: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Encrypted_Media_Extensions
ferrari_pizza: crypts what?
Kuaang: hi. I am looking at Korea
ADivorcedF0rk: lmfao
Hamled2: this, not sure if it's what netflix uses now, but that's the general idea
ADivorcedF0rk: do it then
glitchedoutt: I thought Netflix knew their shit
tribegvng: the method is private atm cause groups are still releasing it scene
glitchedoutt: With ChaosMonkey and all that
Hamled2: there's only so much you can do to hide the data when the ultimate goal of your program is to actually play the video, glitchedoutt
tribegvng: so its still cracked
qin_baba: how high is ur iq
glitchedoutt: Haha fair enough @Hamled2
Hamled2: glitchedoutt chaos monkey is just server-side "resilience testing", the only way I think it interacts with esecurity is kind of like [D]DOS type attacks
ferrari_pizza: but game of thrones isn't Netflix.. 😂
Hamled2: in theory they're more resilient to a specific DoS attack because their systems are already built to withstand any given component dying due to hardware failure or attack or wathever
tribegvng: wouldnt be surprised if they stopped once it gets patched
ferrari_pizza: where are new episodes...
tribegvng: since the releases are trash
ferrari_pizza: vim with a das keyboard... nitemare...
ferrari_pizza: :)
Sylens__: might just start learning vim over learning emacs
unDe4dman: а сколько трансляция идет
Sylens__: youre so fast with this it dont make no since lol
ferrari_pizza: intellij
tribegvng: i split beer on my quickfire and the ctrl key is fucked. not sure what to replace it with tho. custom or?
unDe4dman: !up
unDe4dman: !uptime
tribegvng: good keyboards though damn shame
JonThomasK: react is garbage
Crypod: 1:28
Crypod: @JonThomasK what do you recommend instead?
JonThomasK: if you are going to use a reactive framework? Vue
foxubu: You are still streaming O_O
Crypod: interesting
ferrari_pizza: and he knows all the fckn Unix commands
ferrari_pizza: 😂 😂 😂
tribegvng: i just got someone to build an app but they're using codeigniter i'm dreading it
tribegvng: is it really that bad?
unDe4dman: how many broadcast goes on time?
chase_higgins: Codeigniter isn’t too bad
advil0: hi chase
tribegvng: oh good
chase_higgins: Hey
ferrari_pizza: what is coodeigniter
chase_higgins: Codeigniter is a pho framework
chase_higgins: Php
tribegvng: we're implementing stripe thats the only thing that concerns me . if they find a vuln and put some malicous code on checkout
ferrari_pizza: @chase_higgins ahhh
Hamled2: what does changelist mean in the context of Qira?
advil0: stripe is pretty secure
tribegvng: yeah but if they own it on my side
Hamled2: an object is a key-value store...
chase_higgins: I have stripe implemented in a codeigniter application, it works fine
tribegvng: cant they do like a mimt thing or log anything on the form
Irkanu: If Stripe gets fucked, then a lot of people are fucked.
Hamled2: Object.keys
JonThomasK: ES6 has a generator like python
advil0: yeah stripe is used by TONS of sites
Sylens__: if you dont know go to stack overflow <3
tribegvng: yeah i've used it before
tribegvng: just never with custom code
LilDogMike: whatcha dooooin?
chase_higgins: It’s pretty hard to mess up lol
tribegvng: wasnt there a js vuln on neweeg though
tribegvng: i kinda mean like that not on the payment processor side
Ustunner: What’s good George
tribegvng: https://www.volexity.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/newegg_4.png
mikey9988: monkaS
AshfaqSeyad: hey man
nizero: georege i read this article about u as a kid and it said something about how u would go to ur neighbors houses and "fix" their computers ... is that story true
ferrari_pizza: @tribegvng... what's that credid card func... vuln?
tribegvng: not sure if they actually owned the server
jonnyasl: jonnyasl subscribed with Twitch Prime.
tribegvng: or just the api
tribegvng: @ferrari_pizza https://www.volexity.com/blog/2018/09/19/magecart-strikes-again-newegg/
tribegvng: or was it xss
shafiemukhre: @georgehotz why are you using vim over others?
ferrari_pizza: it's a post command...
ferrari_pizza: json post to Uri...
tribegvng: but they obv were able to write to the checkout page?
tribegvng: to edit insert the code
nizero: george are you moving to SD with the rest of comma.ai team ?
Hamled2: what is the intent of the address readout in the lower-right panel you're working on?
brevan04: Can I hack civic torque with Qira when it is done?
jonnyasl: Haircut?
LilDogMike: do you ever not do this?
tribegvng: @ferrari_pizza if you're a target for attackers best form of defense? bug bounty or something?
tribegvng: H1 etc.
funnnnyyyyy: can i work for you pls
ferrari_pizza: <maybe get a decent cup of coffee>
nizero: use push
tribegvng: push?
Hamled2: George, Object.keys...
JonThomasK: js is cancer anyway, dont blame you for not knowing it in depth
gluecks: is there any good dev environments for python like VS?
tribegvng: electron apps are the best tho so fast
funnnnyyyyy: it's kinda funny i have extra points for my math homework in math at my school and i hacked the teacher computer to get de copy of the homework correction on inthernet and i just did my homework at 2:37am in canada
davidsit_site: today on what never happened
tribegvng: is that a bot
funnnnyyyyy: i send it to my class mates and i charged them 5$ each to get it and i made like 25 i think
Irkanu: something higher in the dam is applying padding
JonThomasK: probably a height: 100% somewhere
tribegvng: bots are getting smarter
Irkanu: can't see b/c your face.
Irkanu: higher in the DOM*
mobilakias: mobilakias subscribed with Twitch Prime.
tribegvng: @georgehotz did macs death shock you?
serhejenos: wow, I'managed to get some sleep and you're still going at it
braktwitch: hi
xune789: Is your motivation for getting a million followers on instagram, to impress thots irl Kappa
unDe4dman: its IDA ?
lucemferro_: are you in support of universal basic income? can i get some of your thoughts about it?
ferrari_pizza: a HashMap for every address.. what are binary size limits?
JonThomasK: qira is awesome
Elinbae: Have you ever thought of creating a cryptocurrency? it seems to be the new cashgrab of the century
unctarheelss: hiii
Juggling_Pro: hey george
joker2k999: the transfer is real...
boneitis: oh shiiiit. will this be the time i finally succeed in installing qira?
JonThomasK: im close to getting qira fully in a docker container so you can run it on any host
Hamled2: JonThomasK what work remains to be done for that
boneitis: giggity
JonThomasK: sorry i mean fixing the docker
joker2k999: looks like the sequel to ddd
jay_al97: your hair got so long
joker2k999: keep the fro bro
Hamled2: do you want to do a source-level debugger view?
joker2k999: peace bro's.
Hamled2: oh yeah I saw some commits about that
Hamled2: right
joker2k999: no.
Hamled2: yes its the PDB for ELF
JonThomasK: i've got a semi-working setup of running qira with docker instead of your local machine so its highly portable (mounts your binary into container)
Hamled2: it's the debug symbol data joker, links the assembly instructions to source code lines
joker2k999: OHcoolz
Hamled2: goodnight
serhejenos: have a good night george